嘿 你听说过Van Nuys动漫节吗?
Hey, have you ever heard of the Van Nuys Comic-Con?
听说过啊
‭Yeah.
就是卖点周边 找几个没名儿的四线明星去撑撑场子
It's a dinky little convention where they sell collectibles
其实根本没什么人会去 你问这个干什么?
and get sad D-list celebrities to appear. Why?
他们邀请我去签名
I got asked to sign autographs there.
这么棒!
That's awesome!
是 "杀人恶猿" 那部电影吗?
Is this for Serial Ape-ist?
可能是猴子电影
Well, it could be for the monkey movie.
也可能是我那个痔疮药的广告
It could be my hemorrhoid commercial.
毕竟我也没别的作品了
The list does not go on.
- 动漫节是什么时候?  - 管它呢
- When is it?  - It doesn't matter.
我才不去
I'm not doing it.
为什么不去啊?
What? Why not?
你自己说的 去的人都是没名儿的四线明星
You just said yourself, it's sad.
是啊 不过还没到可悲的地步
Yeah, but it's not pathetic.
我觉得做人 只要不可悲就行了
That's where I draw the line.
来嘛! 会很好玩的
Come on! We'll have fun.
我也不知道
I don't know.
到时候会有一群书呆子围着你转
You'll have nerds fawning all over you.
要是这都吸引不了你 那我们的婚姻岂不是个笑话
If you don't love that, this marriage is in trouble.
大概 见见粉丝也没坏处吧
I guess it wouldn't hurt to meet some fans
还能挣点外快
and make a little extra money.
是啊
Yeah.
天啊! 乔治·卢卡斯也会去呢...
Wow! An appearance by George Lucas...
电影"星球大战"的导演
不对... 是他的皮肤病医生
's dermatologist.
- 那我也想要他的签名  - 好吧
- Oh, I want that autograph.  - Oh, yeah.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第十季第6集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 万圣节的南瓜酥
校对: 番茄酱满脸猫呗
翻译:南瓜酥 言小默 肉肉君 李小宝Licht
既然我们都同居了 我觉得我们应该找个机会
You know, with us living together, maybe we could
邀请别人来家里做做客
think about having people over.
我们家里经常有外人来啊
We have people over all the time.
物业的人会来 外卖小哥会来...
We have the maintenance people, the pizza delivery man...
还有那个送快递的人
that UPS driver who feels the need to ask
非要强行跟我打招呼
how parts of me are hanging.
你不要岔开话题
You know what I meant.
好吧
All right, fine.
就算
Let's say that
我们要请人来家里玩
we were to entertain people.
你想怎么玩?
What type of gathering did you have in mind?
聚餐吗? 那么 是吃午饭?
Huh? A meal? Lunch?
早午饭? 还是晚饭?
Brunch? Dinner?
或者一起喝下午茶? 是正式的那种吗? 嗯?
Afternoon tea? A formal tea? Hmm?
还是你想开趴? 那你想开哪种趴?
Is it a party? And if so, what kind of party?
是有鸡尾酒的聚会?
Is it a cocktail party?
微波炉食品聚会餐?
A Tupperware party?
对了... 还是说你想开一个惊喜派对?
Ooh, yeah... is it a surprise party?
不过最好可别是
Oh, I hope it's not
传说中的 "西海岸派对" 因为歌里说
a West Coast party, 'cause according to
西海岸的派对根本停不下来
the man on the radio, a West Coast party don't stop.
我的锅 我不应该提这事 对不起
I'm sorry I mentioned it.
别这么说啦 你负责提建议
Oh, don't be. You get your hopes up,
我负责否决 这就是团队合作嘛
I knock them down. That's called teamwork.
它在踢我
That's a kick.
真的在踢我
That's an actual kick.
你干什么呢?
What are you doing?
我感觉宝宝在踢我
I felt a kick.
你肚子里有个孩子
There's a baby in there.
是嘛 原来我放肚子里了啊
Oh, yeah, that's where I put it.
我是说 我知道你怀孕了
Oh, I mean, I know you're pregnant.
但是...
I just...
我从来没意识到 怀孕就是
never connected the idea of pregnancy
你肚子里有个真的孩子了
and you actually having a baby.
你真的是麻省理工毕业的?
Which MIT did you go to?
天啊 我们还没准备好迎接这个孩子啊!
Oh, God, we are not ready to have an infant in this house!
没有婴儿床 没有尿布
We don't have a crib, we don't have diapers.
也没做婴儿防护措施
We're not baby-proofed.
路上随便一个人都能到我们家来掀马桶盖!
Anyone can just walk in off the street and lift our toilet lids!
Howie 我们有的是时间慢慢做准备呢
Howie, we have time to do all that stuff.
是嘛?
Do we?
你看看你
Look at you.
Willy Wonka马上就要把你推进榨汁间了
Willy Wonka would roll you to the juicing room.
"查理的巧克力工厂"电影中有专门榨果汁的房间
现在我也想踢你了
The next person kicking you will be me.
快睡吧
Good night.
我们这附近有好学校么...?
Are we even in a good school...?
嗷!
Ow!
我警告过你了 不怪我
I warned you, and I did it.
这都是什么?
What's all this?
这些都是给你的签名会准备的材料...
Oh, everything we need for your autograph session...
你的海报 还有马克笔
head shots, markers.
Lenard 你准备的这么齐全是挺好的
Okay. Leonard, it's sweet you're excited about this,
但是只要有一个人要我的签名 那就是奇迹了
but it'll be a miracle if one person asks for my autograph.
你开什么玩笑?
Are you kidding?
我曾经花了20刀买Theo Sassler的签名
I once paid $20 for Theo Sassler's signature.
- 那是谁?  - 我也不知道
- Who's that?  - Oh, I don't even know.
只是觉得他的名字挺好听的 Theo Sassler!
I just liked his name. Theo Sassler!
来来来 给你看这个
Oh, and look at this.
我还准备了找零神器
I even got a change maker.
小美女 想换多少零钱啊?
How much change you want, little lady?
讲真 我现在想换的可不只是零钱
Oh, there's so much I want to change.
你要是想换1刀的硬币 尽管来找我
Yeah, well, if it's a dollar, you're in luck.
这是什么情况?
What's going on here?
你说你想邀请别人来家里做客
You expressed an interest in having people over,
我觉得我反对的太快了
and I feel I dismissed it too quickly.
所以 我亲自动手
So, I took matters
准备了早午餐 还邀请了几个人过来
into my own hands, and I arranged a brunch.
你太好了
Well, that's so nice.
都有谁要来啊?
Who's coming?
Stuart 地质实验室的Bert
Oh, uh, Stuart, Bert from the geology lab,
还有楼下的Petrescu太太
and Mrs. Petrescu from downstairs.
你是说住在二楼的那个罗马尼亚女士吗?
You mean the Romanian lady on the second floor?
是的
Yes.
有个有意思的事:
Oh, fun story:
她是跟十个兄弟姐妹一起长大的
she grew up with ten siblings.
也有可能是跟企鹅 她的英语简直穷凶极恶
Or possibly penguins. Her English is atrocious.
这组合还挺怪的
That's an odd mix of people.
这是我们第一次作为主人招待别人
Well, for our first time hosting,
我觉得实施一次试验还挺明智的
I thought it would be wise to conduct a trial run.
你知道的 就好像那次
You know, like how I practiced
我去万圣节鬼屋之前
for that Halloween haunted house
用公交车站的卫生间来做练习一样
by going into the bathroom at the bus station.
但你后来也没去那个鬼屋啊
You never went into that haunted house.
你也没看见车站里跳出来吓我一跳的东西
You never saw what jumped out at me at the bus station.
好吧 谢谢你 Sheldon
Well, thank you, Sheldon.
这是个有趣的惊喜
This is a fun surprise.
而真正的惊喜是
Oh. Well, the real surprise is
你对于我擅长惊喜表示惊讶
how surprised you are that I'm great at surprises.
可是那完全不是惊喜啊
Well, that's not a surprise at all.
我是说 如果我知道你擅长惊喜的话
I mean, if I knew you were good at surprises,
那我就会对这个惊喜有所预料
I would have expected the surprise,
从而不为它而感到惊喜了
and therefore not have been surprised.
但正是因为我得到了惊喜 所以我不知道你擅长惊喜
But as it is, I didn't know,
所以我对此表示的惊讶就不应该让你感到惊讶
and therefore my surprise should be unsurprising.
别让我变得这么欲火难耐 客人都要来了
Don't get me all randy. Guests are on the way.
嗨
Hi.
嘿 你们刚刚去哪儿啦?
Hey, where you been?
哦 我们刚刚去为宝宝买了点东西
Oh, we went and did a little shopping for the baby.
等你看到我们买到的婴儿床就知道了
Wait till you see the crib we found.
你们没经过我就自己买了个婴儿床?
You bought a crib without me?
- 你会喜欢的  - 真的
- You're gonna love it.  - Yeah.
它是市场上评价最高的一款
It's the highest rated one on the market.
我都不会管它叫婴儿床
I wouldn't even call it a crib.
我会叫它宝宝专用孤独堡垒
I'd call it a Fortress of Solitude for babies.
听上去很贵啊
Sounds expensive.
好吧 我可能是
Okay, well, I may have gone
有点花过头了 但是安全是无价的嘛
a bit overboard, but you can't put a price on safety.
不过假如真想标价 它后面的零比你想象的要多
Though if you did, it's more zeroes than you're expecting.
但是这是能买到的最安全的婴儿床了
But it's the safest crib you can buy.
而且如果你不喜欢的话 我们还可以把它退回去
And if you don't like it, we can return it.
- 好吧  - 用我们新买的小面包车退
- Fine.  - In our new minivan.
哎呀 午饭是什么啊?
Hey, what's for lunch?
你买了辆小面包车?!
You bought a minivan?!
是为了宝宝嘛 而且我也没买
It's for the baby, and I didn't buy it.
车行把它借给了我
The dealer loaned it to me
说我有24个小时试驾
for a 24-hour test drive.
不过车后备箱被婴儿床磨得挺厉害的
Though we did ding up the back pretty good with the crib,
所以你们可能要买辆小面包车了
so you might have bought a minivan.
我可不想开那个 那也太妈妈款了
I don't want to drive that. It's such a mom car.
可是车行的人说
The guy at the dealership said
这种车已经不再是只为妈妈专用的了
they're not just for moms anymore.
可是讲道理
Then again,
他也确实以为你是我老公
he did think you were my husband.
他们在做超声波的时候都这么想
They thought it at the ultrasound.
车行这么想有问题吗?
Why not at the car dealership?
我以前从没在桌子的这半边待过啊
Never been on this side of the table before.
我觉得自己大权在握
I feel powerful.
真的吗?
Really?
我觉得我像是在为了队里的新制服卖糖果
I feel like I'm selling candy so our team can get new uniforms.
好吧 那一张黑白的签名海报是4.75美金
Okay, so it's $4.75 for a signed black-and-white
然后彩色的是9.95美金
and $9.95 for a color.
对 为什么不直接用五块和十块啊?
Right. Why not five and ten bucks?
可是我带了我的找零神奇啊 让我嘚瑟嘚瑟嘛
Well, I brought my moneymaker. Let me shake it.
哎呀 那个人看过来了
Hey, that guy's looking over here.
你觉得他会是你的第一个顾客吗?
Oh. You think he's your first autograph?
我不知道 高冷一点 他过来了 他过来了
I don't know. Be cool. He's coming. He's coming.
- 嗨!  - 嗨
- Hi!  - Hi.
我大爱你的电影
I love your movie.
谢谢
Well, thanks.
那绝对得是我平生看过的
It has got to be one of the worst things
最烂的东西之一
I've ever seen in my life.
你的爱简直让我困惑
Your love confuses me.
你想要张签名照吗?
Would you like an autograph?
好呀
Sure.
好嘞 你想让我把它写给谁呢?
Okay. Who do I make it out to?
给Daniel
Daniel.
- 行  - 我必须得问问
- Okay.  - I have to ask.
你当时是故意往差了演
Were you trying to be that bad,
还是你就真的是个烂演员呢?
or are you just a terrible actress?
这话也没能解开我的困惑
That did not clear things up.
一共4.75
That'll be $4.75.
不用找了
Keep the change.
可是我...
But I... Oh.
刚刚那完全算不上好啊
Nothing about that was good.
没错
Mm-mm.
这没什么可怕的 Sheldon
There's nothing to be afraid of, Sheldon.
软木塞的平均速度可是有25英里每小时呢
The average cork speed is 25 miles per hour.
25英里/时≈40公里/时
如果这个速度在学校周围都算是太快了的话
If that is too fast around a school,
那它在厨房里也肯定太快了
it is certainly too fast around a kitchen.
可是已经过去15分钟了
Been 15 minutes. Just sayin'.
好吧 我行的
Okay. I can do this.
给我点时间...
Just give me a moment...
含羞草鸡尾酒来了
Mimosas coming up.
我曾经把一罐橙汁放在冰箱里放了太久
I once left orange juice in my fridge so long,
导致喝起来也像含羞草鸡尾酒
so it tasted like a mimosa.
那得放了多久了啊?
How old was it?
这很难说啊
It's hard to say.
我喝了它以后就不记得了
I don't remember much after I drank it.
你要来一杯吗 Petrescu太太?
Would you like one, Mrs. Petrescu?
是的 喝酒是为了乐趣和好朋友 这是Applebee说的
Yes. Drink is fun and good friends-- Applebee's.
Applebee是美国一家连锁餐厅
她的英语是从电视上学的
She's learning English from TV.
电视很好 你继续吧
TV, good. Now back to you.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
嗨 Stuart
Hi, Stuart.
这个是给你的
These are for you.
哦 它们真漂亮 谢谢你
Oh, they're pretty. Thank you.
Stuart 这是加州理工学院地理实验室的Bert
Stuart, this is Bert from the Caltech geology lab,
这个是住在楼下的Petrescu女士
and this is Mrs. Petrescu from downstairs.
很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you.
- 你好  - 你好
- Hello.  - Hey.
所以说 我错过了什么?
So, what did I miss?
呃 我们看Sheldon开瓶子
Eh, we watched Sheldon try to open a bottle
开了十五分钟
for 15 minutes.
十五分钟可以给你的汽车保险打八五折
15 minutes can save you 15% or more on car insurance.
还有谁要来吗?
Anybody else coming to this thing? Uh...
- 你叫什么名字?  - Jeff
- What's your name?  - Jeff.
好
Okay.
我最喜欢的部分是你洗澡那一幕
My favorite part is your shower scene.
今天已经听过好多遍了
Been hearing that a lot today.
我还把它做成了我手机的屏保
I even have a screen grab on my phone.
没错 咪咪在那呢
Yep, there they are.
嗯 换下一个吧
Okay, let's keep it moving.
给你
Here you go.
我应该打他一拳
Should've punched that guy.
那去吧 他就在那呢
Well, go ahead. He's right over there.
为什么要说出来? 就不能让我展现一下雄风?
Why do you do that? Can't you let me have my moment?
- 你好  - 你好
- Hello.  - Hi.
我喜欢你的电影
I like your movies.
谢谢你!
Thank you!
我两部都看了
I saw both of them.
我猜我们还是在讨论电影
I assume we're still talking about the movies,
但这一天下来 谁知道呢
but after today, who knows.
我可以和你拍一张合照吗?
You think I could get a picture of us?
哦 当然
Oh, sure.
还有 呃 你能不能
And, uh, could you be
亲我一下?
giving me a kiss?
不 她不能亲...
No. She cannot kiss...
你们这些人都什么毛病?!
What is wrong with you people?!
- Leonard...  - 不 不 不 这一点都不好
- Leonard...  - No, no, no. It's not okay.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是他丈夫
I'm her husband.
你才不是呢
No, you're not.
我就是
I am.
对 他真的是
Yeah, he really is.
我才不信
No.
它有后置摄像头 还有DVD播放器
It's got a rearview camera, there's a DVD player,
看看这个
oh, and check this out.
感觉我们就像是住在未来一样
It's like we're living in the future!
嘿 给她演示后备箱! 给她演示后备箱!
Hey, show her the trunk! Show her the trunk!
想象一下 你一只手抱着孩子
Imagine this: you've got the baby in one hand,
另一只手拎着菜 你在想
groceries in the other, and you're thinking,
"我怎么才能把后备箱打开呢?"
"How am I gonna open this trunk?"
我可能会想 "我的丈夫呢
I'm probably thinking, "Where's my husband,
他为什么不来帮我?"
and why isn't he helping me?"
如果你只用脚踢一下就能开后备箱的话
You don't need my help when you can open the trunk
你都用不着我帮忙
with a simple kick of the foot.
不 你弄错了 要温柔地踢
No, it's a gentle kick; you're doing it wrong.
来 把东西都给我
Here. Give me those.
是不是要绕一个圈?
Uh, maybe it was more of a circle?
那人以为你们是一对儿真是太奇怪了
It's weird that guy thought you were a couple.
- 太棒了!  - 是啊!
- Yes!  - Yes!
看到了吗?
See?
多简单 再看看这么大的储物空间
Easy. And look at all this cargo space.
这样吧 把婴儿床拿出来
You know, we'll get the crib out
你就可以试驾了
and you can take it for a test-drive.
我告诉你 这个商务车会是...
I'm telling you, this van is gonna be...
你后背受伤了吗?
Oh, is it your back?
嗯... 是的
Uh... yeah.
没事 我们上车吧 看看GPS
Anyway, let's just get in and see if the GPS
能不能把我们带到最近的急救室去
can take us to the nearest emergency room.
所以直到Amy的公寓修好前
So until Amy's apartment is fixed,
我们都要一起住在这
she and I are living here together.
我之前也和我女朋友住在一起
I lived with my old girlfriend.
她也是个地质学家
She was a geologist, too.
你俩合不来吗?
Things didn't work out?
我有一天下班回家发现她把所有东西都拿走了
I came home from work one day and she had taken everything.
我警告你们
I'm warning you,
把收藏的好石头藏好
hide your good rocks.
我妹夫也拿走全部东西了
My sister's husband took all her things, too.
故事十一点整开始
Story at 11:00.
真的吗? 没人来了?
Really, no one else is coming?
就是这些了
Oh, this is it.
你们是试验品
You are the practice round.
试验品? 试验什么?
Practice round? For-for what?
不是 他意思是
Uh, no. He-he just means that
你们是我们第一个想到的人
you were the first people we thought of.
是的
You know, exactly.
我们之前从来没有招待过早午餐
We've never thrown a brunch before,
我们想试一试 并解决其中缺陷
and I wanted to work out all the kinks.
所以 我就是只小白鼠
So, I'm like a lab rat
然后你们真正的朋友们才会过来?
before your real friends come over?
发现了吗 你的话没错
You see, your words sound reasonable,
但你的表情看起来很生气
but your face looks angry.
帮我一下 这个我不擅长
Help me out here. This is not where I shine.
听着 Stuart
Stuart,
你知道你是我们最喜欢的人之一
you know you're one of our favorite people.
发现了吗 你看起来很真诚
Okay, now, see, you look sincere,
但你说出来的东西全是错的
but your words are completely false.
我很高兴我们做了这次实验
I'm glad we did this test run.
这顿早午餐太棒了!
These brunches are wild!
但是你怎么让她答应和你约会的?
But how did you get her to go out with you?
她搬到了我对面住
Well, she moved in across the hall.
然后他就开始步步为营
And he started to slowly wear me down.
没错
Mm-hmm.
就像滴水穿石一样
Like a river carves a canyon.
但是这小水滴总给我看他的口袋妖怪卡片
Yeah, except the river kept showing me his Pokemon cards.
可以走了吗?
Ready to go?
等等 这人在跟我说
Hang on. This guy's telling me
他是怎么把杀人恶猿里面那女的弄到手的
how he got the Serial Ape-ist girl to marry him.
就这人?
This guy?
带着零钱机的这人?
But he's wearing a change maker.
我觉得特别性感
I think it's hot.
没错
That's right.
我是她的零钱干爹
I'm her change daddy.
我在想什么啊?
What was I thinking?
Wolowitzes家族从不具备提升重物的能力
Wolowitzes are not a lifting people!
我们都是花钱雇人的!
We tip the lifting people!
我们真的有必要去急诊室
Do we really have to sit for hours
一呆几个小时吗?
in the emergency room?
他们只会给你冰块和止痛药的
They're just gonna give you ice and Advil
就像上次一样
like last time.
如果我坐轮椅了 你会很痛苦的
You're gonna feel terrible when I'm in a wheelchair.
另外 轮椅这玩意儿 在这辆保姆车里
Which, by the way, would fit easily in the back
还真是合适得不行
of this award-winning minivan.
知道了 我们去急诊室 别再给我推销这辆车了
Fine, we'll go to the E.R. Just stop selling me on the van.
你说得对 它可以自卖自夸
You're right. It sells itself.
你必须承认 这一路上还挺顺的
You have to admit, it's a pretty smooth ride.
我比较希望能安静一点
I was hoping it'd be quieter.
如果你生孩子的时候有现在一半的疼
If childbirth is half this bad,
你就完蛋了!
you are so screwed!
我们到了吗?! 快了
Are we there yet?! Soon.
为什么要这么久啊?!
Why is it taking so long?!
Howard 看DVD的屏幕
H... Howard, Howard, look at the DVD screen.
我给你放了蝙蝠侠动画系列 你的最爱!
I put on Batman: The Animated Series. Your favorite!
我已经疼到看不了动画...
I'm in too much pain to watch cartoo...
喔! 这集不错
Oh! This is a good one.
我照顾他的时间
I've been babysitting him
可是比你长得多了
way longer than you have.
好吧 不就一辆破车嘛 买就买
Fine. I'll buy the stupid van.
这是我吃过的味道最好的薄饼了
This is the best blintz I've ever had.
谢谢你
Oh. Thank you.
这已经把之前那尴尬的转折
It almost makes up for the incredibly awkward turn
弥补得差不多了
things took earlier.
我... 我想我还是先走了
You know what, I... I think I'm just gonna go.
别 Stuart 别走啊
No, Stuart, don't.
不... 我把你和Sheldon当作我的家人
No, I... I consider you and Sheldon like my family,
但我都拿不准你们是不是把我当朋友
and I'm not even sure you think of me as a friend.
你知道这是什么感觉吗?
You have any idea how that feels?
我们很抱歉
We're so sorry.
每个人都是最后才会想起我
I'm always the last one anybody thinks of.
不是这样的
Well, no, that's not true.
有的时候大家最后才想起Koothrappali
I mean, sometimes it's Koothrappali.
但说出来又不好
But we're not supposed to say that 'cause
因为他不受大众喜爱
he's a minority.
再见
Bye.
Stuart 等等
Stuart, wait.
我知道被人忽视和遗忘的滋味
I do know what it feels like to be left out.
我也知道
I know how it feels, too.
行了 这是我和他之间的事 你一边儿凉快去
All right, this is about me and him; you're not part of it.
Stuart 或许我们是有点不重视你了
Stuart, perhaps we do take you for granted,
这样做是不对的
and that is not acceptable.
但请相信你确实是我们圈子里
Please know that you truly are a valuable member
珍贵的一员
of our social group.
谢谢
Thank you.
好了 我提议大家举杯
You know, in fact, I'd like to propose a toast.
敬Stuart
To Stuart.
一个好人
A fine man,
一个好朋友 一个很棒的客人
a good friend and a wonderful guest.
说的是 干杯
Hear, hear. Cheers.
干杯 于录音棚观众之前拍摄
Cheers. Filmed before a live studio audience.
这就是一个患有哮喘的矮子科学家
And that is how a short asthmatic scientist
攻陷了一个冰山美人的故事
landed a stone cold fox.
哇哦
Oh. Whoa.
我简直难以想象你可以向同一个人
I didn't know you can propose to the same person
求那么多次婚
so many times.
第三次我是用空中写字求的婚
The third time, I did it in skywriting,
但她头都没抬一下
but she never looked up.
还有一次 是我跟他求的婚
You know, once, I proposed to him.
是啊 我拒绝了
Yeah. I said no.
为什么?
Why?
我就是想让她多费点事儿
I just wanted to make her work for it.
没事 我们秋后算账
Yeah, that's gonna cost you later.
等等 她和你在一起是因为你有钱吗?
Hang on. Is she just with you because you're rich?
她赚的比我多了去了!
She makes more money than I do!
什么? 你也太强了吧!
What?! Who are you?!
你知道我还喜欢你什么吗?
Do you know what else I love about you?
什么?
Hmm?
你... 的书法 简直无懈可击!
Y... Your handwriting is impeccable!
谢谢你能注意到这个!
Thank you for noticing!
我说真的 我说真的
No, I mean it. I mean it.
你就仿佛拥有标签机的灵魂
It's like you have the soul of a label maker.
你知道我喜欢你什么吗?
You know what I love about you?
什么?
Hmm?
你出门一定会随身携带回形针!
You never leave the house without a paper clip!
你永远不知道什么时候就会出现两张纸
You never know when two pieces of paper
需要临时在左上角固定起来
might temporarily need fastening in the top left corner.
我还喜欢你从来不说脏话
I also love how you never use swear words.
事实证明嘛
You know, it turns out,
不说脏话 你也一样可以伤人于无形
you can hurt people just as well without 'em.
有没有人来帮我收拾收拾这些东西啊
Maybe I can get a little help putting some of this stuff away.
淡定
Oh, calm down.
我已经 "收拾" 了五杯这个了
I already put away five of these!
看见了吗?
You see?
开口没脏话 文明你我他
No muss, no fuss, not a single cuss.